Punya Jayarajan

Graphic Designer and Front end developer

Portfolio Website: bit.ly/punyajayarajan

Email Me: punyajayarajan@gmail.com LinkedIn: <u>Punya Jayarajan</u> Phone Number: +91 6282937874

Github: punvai

ABOUT ME

Passionate and driven web and graphic designer with notable internship experiences in this field. Excited about the opportunity to contribute expertise in frontend development and visual design. Offers excellent multitasking skills and extraordinary time management abilities.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BRANDisam - FrontEnd Developer

Nov 2023 - Jan 2024

- Completed a three-month Frontend Developer Internship at BRANDisam, contributing to a Mern stack project for a Psychometric Assessment System
- Focused on crafting UI-UX design and frontend for both mobile and laptop versions of the website.
- Deepened understanding of Figma and strengthened technical skills through hands-on experience and effectively working with team members.

Grow More Tech - Graphic Design Intern

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

- Completed a three-month graphic design internship at Growmoretech IT solution, gaining valuable experience in engaging directly with clients to bring their ideas to life.
- Expanded skills and knowledge in graphic design, exploring various aspects of product development.
- Designed various Catalog, PPT, Slide and Website content during the tenure.

Session With Sumit - Graphic Design Intern

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

- Successfully completed a 3-month graphic design internship at Session with Sumit, gaining invaluable professional growth.
- Created Educational and YouTube Promotional Content during the tenure.

EDUCATION

Government College Of Engineering Kannur - APJ Abdul Kalam Technological University

2020 - Present

• BTech in Electronics And Communication Engineering

Anjarakandy Higher Secondary School - Kerala State Board

2018 - 2020

- Biology Science
- Percentage 93.33%

Sreepuram English Medium School Kannur - ICSE Board

2017 - 2018

• Percentage - 85.6%

SKILLS

Graphic Design - Photoshop, Illustrator, Canva, Figma, Adobe XD **Web Development -** HTML, CSS, Js, Bootstrap, WordPress **Programming Languages -** Python, C(Basic), Java(Basic) **Soft Skills -** Multitasking, Leadership, Problem-solving, Working Independently, Teamwork

Calypso GCEK Website

- Designed and developed an informative website for Calypso GCEK, a space club at Government College of Engineering Kannur.
- Demonstrated leadership and technical skills, significantly expanding outreach and promoting space exploration initiatives.
- Link: https://calvpso-gcek.github.io/calvpsogcek

SHE State Level Launch Website

2023

2023

- Developed and launched the SHE State Level Launch website.
- The website was inaugurated by the Honorable Minister of Higher Education R. Bindu, with the aim of uniting the SHE community across multiple engineering colleges in Kerala.
- Link: https://sheacek.aithub.io/SHE-State-Level-Launch

Sanjeevani - Ambulance Traffic Signal Alert

2022

- Designed a GPS tracker system facilitating path clearance for ambulance vehicles.
- Developed an innovative Web-App for real-time tracking of nearby hospitals, available beds, and doctors.
- Implemented an alert system to dynamically control traffic signals, ensuring prioritized ambulance routes during emergencies.
- Link: https://punyaj.github.io/ambulance-traffic-signal-alert

Covid wikipedia - CoWiki

2022

- Developed during the Covid Crisis Hackathon, CoWiki 2022 is a comprehensive Covid Wikipedia, serving as a one-stop solution for Covid-related information.
- Provides real-time updates on cases, hospital bed availability, and relevant news.
- Link: https://punyaj.github.io/Covid-Encyclopedia

ACTIVITIES & ASSOCIATIONS

CERTIFICATION

NPTEL Course -

2023 - Present

- Technical Coordinator SHE GCEK
- Technical Coordinator Calypso GCEK

2022 - 2023

- Vice Chair Calypso GCEK
- Lead Technical Support and Web Admin SHE
- Design Lead NSS GCEK

2021 - 2022

- Web Admin SHE GCEK
- Outreach Lead TinkerHub GCEK Founding Member

 Programming, Data Structures And Algorithms Using Python

Revertech IT Solutions -

- 7 Days Wordpress Internship Course
- Gained valuable experience in building websites using WordPress.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCES

DEV-WEB 2.0 & DEV-WEB 2.1:

Feb 2023 - May 2023

Organizer & Mentor (10 Day Web Development Bootcamp)

• Orchestrated in the completion of two successful 10-day Web Development Bootcamps at GCE Kannur as part of empowering female students under SHE GCEK.